A Guide to the Papers of Virginius Dabney
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7690-aj
Papers of Virginius Dabney 1983-1986
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7690-aj
9 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1988 October 17
Container List
- Manuscripts
  - Far Echoes From the Old Arcades, ca. 1983; TMs (Box Box 1)
  - The Last Review The Confederate Reunion, Richmond, 1932 (Late Draft), 1984; TMs (Box Box 1)
  - Pistols and Pointed Pens, [ca. 1986?]; Notes (Box Box 1)
  - Pistols and Pointed Pens, Original Manuscript (2 folders), [ca. 1986?]; TMs (Box Box 1)
  - Pistols and Pointed Pens, Original Manuscript - Edited, 1987; TMs (Box Box 1)
  - Pistols and Pointed Pens, Computer Printout, 1987; TMs (electrostatic copy) (Box Box 2)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, A Sesquicentenniel History, Original Manuscript (3 folders), ca. 1987; TMs (Box Box 2)
  - Virginius Dabney's Virginia (A selection of previously published articles by Dabney re Virginia), [ca. 1985]; Printed (Box Box 3)
  - Virginius Dabney's Virginia (2 folders), 1986; TMs (setting copy) (Box Box 3)